[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "categoria": "Funkos",
        "marca": "Pokemon",
        "nombre": "Charmander",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "SKU": "AES5456SD1",
        "precio": 2700,
        "stock": 3,
        "descuento": 10,
        "cuotas": 3,
        "images_front": "pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
        "images_back": "pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "nombre": "Dragonite",
        "marca": "Pokemon",
        "images_front": "pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
        "images_back": "pokemon/dragonite-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "precio": 2500,
        "SKU": "AD5456SD2",
        "cuotas": 3,
        "stock": 12,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "nombre": "Pidgeotto",
        "marca": "Pokemon",
        "images_front": "pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
        "images_back": "pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "precio": 3000,
        "SKU": "ES5456SD3",
        "cuotas": 3,
        "stock": 6,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "nombre": "Pikachu",
        "marca": "Pokemon",
        "images_front": "pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
        "images_back": "pokemon/pikachu-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "precio": 3500,
        "SKU": "DS5456SD4",
        "cuotas": 3,
        "stock": 5,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "nombre": "Vulpix",
        "marca": "Pokemon",
        "images_front": "pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
        "images_back": "pokemon/vulpix-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "precio": 3550,
        "SKU": "CS5456SD5",
        "cuotas": 3,
        "stock": 19,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "nombre": "Baby Yoda",
        "marca": "Star wars",
        "images_front": "star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
        "images_back": "star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star wars",
        "precio": 4000,
        "SKU": "BS545SD6",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 8,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "nombre": "Bobbafeth",
        "marca": "Star wars",
        "images_front": "star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
        "images_back": "star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star wars",
        "precio": 4500,
        "SKU": "AS235676SD7",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 23,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "nombre": "Luke",
        "marca": "Star wars",
        "images_front": "star-wars/luke-1.webp",
        "images_back": "star-wars/luke-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star wars",
        "precio": 2500,
        "SKU": "AS54F45SD8",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 22,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "nombre": "Trooper",
        "marca": "Star wars",
        "images_front": "star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
        "images_back": "star-wars/trooper-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star wars",
        "precio": 1500,
        "SKU": "AS54356SD9",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 25,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "nombre": "Harry",
        "marca": "Harry Potter",
        "images_front": "harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
        "images_back": "harry-potter/harry-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "precio": 2500,
        "SKU": "ASF4556SD10",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 20,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "nombre": "Hermione",
        "marca": "Harry Potter",
        "images_front": "harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
        "images_back": "harry-potter/hermione-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "precio": 3000,
        "SKU": "AS544566SD11",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 10,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "nombre": "Luna",
        "marca": "Harry Potter",
        "images_front": "harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
        "images_back": "harry-potter/luna-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "precio": 3550,
        "SKU": "AS5456SD12",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 18,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "nombre": "Snape-patronus",
        "marca": "Harry Potter",
        "images_front": "harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
        "images_back": "harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
        "precio": 5000,
        "SKU": "AS5436SD13",
        "cuotas": 6,
        "stock": 15,
        "descuento": 10,
        "categoria": "Funkos"
    }
]
